export const quiz6 = {
    topic: 'Eating',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    questions: [
        {
            question: "How often you been feeling anxious or upset about your body or eating?",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "Have you been excessively exercising to try to lose weight or change your body?",
            answers: ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question: "Have you feel pressured to look a certain way or lose weight?",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "Have you been avoiding social events or situations that involve food?",
            answers: ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question: "How often you experienced any physical symptoms like dizziness or fatigue?",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "Do you follow obsessive rituals around food and eating, such as only drinking out of a certain cup",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          },
          {
            question: "How often you feel guilty or ashamed after eating?",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "Have you been engaging in secretive behaviors related to food, like hiding food or eating alone?",
            answers: ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question: "Are you experiencing any physical symptoms like stomach pain, constipation, or heartburn that you think might be related to your eating habits?",
            answers: ["Yes","No"]
          },
          {
            question: "Have you been isolating yourself from friends or family?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          }
    ],
  }